Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪من يدري إن كنت دافئًا أم باردًا♪
♪Years of companionship vanish like mist♪
♪سنوات من الرفقة تتلاشى مثل الضباب♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪كم عدد الطرق التي يجب أن يسلكها الحب العميق؟♪
♪The returned soul wears robes of regret♪
♪الروح العائدة ترتدي رداء الندم♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪إزالة الغبار بموجة♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪ ريح أو لا ريح، أفكر فيك♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=خارج الحلقة=
=Episode 20=
=الحلقة 20=
Step aside.
تنحى.
City Lord is here!
سيد المدينة هنا!
City Lord!
سيد المدينة!
City Lord, don't open the gates!
سيد المدينة، لا تفتح الأبواب!
Quiet!
هادئ!
Our livelihood in Jin City is precarious.
معيشتنا في مدينة جين محفوفة بالمخاطر.
How can we provide relief to refugees?
كيف يمكننا تقديم الإغاثة للاجئين؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
What if they bring diseases into the city,
ماذا لو جلبوا الأمراض إلى المدينة؟
then what to do?
إذن ماذا أفعل؟
Exactly, City Lord.
بالضبط يا سيد المدينة.
Everyone, I understand your concerns.
الجميع، أنا أفهم مخاوفكم.
Jin City faces threats both in and out.
تواجه مدينة جين التهديدات من الداخل والخارج.
I don't want any more complications.
لا أريد المزيد من التعقيدات.
But those refugees outside
لكن هؤلاء اللاجئين في الخارج
are living people.
هم أناس أحياء.
Imagine,
يتصور،
if those refugees
إذا كان هؤلاء اللاجئين
were your own family members,
كانوا أفراد عائلتك،
your siblings,
إخوتك،
your spouses, or your children,
زوجاتك أو أطفالك
would you want to see them displaced
هل تريد أن تراهم نازحين؟
starving outside the city?
جائع خارج المدينة؟
They're not citizens of Jin City,
إنهم ليسوا مواطنين لمدينة جين،
but still of Central Plains.
ولكن لا يزال من السهول الوسطى.
You are right, City Lord,
أنت على حق يا سيد المدينة،
But what about our livelihood?
ولكن ماذا عن معيشتنا؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Consider our livelihood too, City Lord.
فكر في معيشتنا أيضًا، يا سيد المدينة.
Everyone, I hereby vow to you.
الجميع، أنا أقسم لكم بهذا.
Refugees will be settled in designated areas.
سيتم توطين اللاجئين في مناطق مخصصة.
They won't disrupt your lives.
لن يعطلوا حياتكم.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
I'll station heavy guards at the granary.
سأقوم بنشر حراس مشددين في المخزن.
No food plunder will be allowed.
لن يُسمح بنهب المواد الغذائية.
Not a single person shall go hungry.
لن يجوع أحد.
Those who contribute provisions
أولئك الذين يساهمون في الأحكام
will receive tax exemptions this season.
سيحصلون على إعفاءات ضريبية هذا الموسم.
- Good! - Very good!
- جيد! - جيد جدًا!
Everyone, you shall know
الجميع، يجب أن تعرفوا
that Mobei is eyeing us,
أن موباي يراقبنا،
having conquered
بعد أن غزت
multiple cities surrounding Jin City.
مدن متعددة تحيط بمدينة جين.
Now more than ever,
الآن أكثر من أي وقت مضى،
we must stand united
يجب علينا أن نقف متحدين
to go against our enemy.
للذهاب ضد عدونا.
I believe we will
أعتقد أننا سوف
eventually bring lasting peace to borders.
تحقيق السلام الدائم على الحدود في نهاية المطاف.
- Well said!
- أحسنت القول!
Good!
جيد!
I believe that one day,
أعتقد أنه في يوم من الأيام،
people will interact
الناس سوف يتفاعلون
without suspicion or doubt.
بدون شك أو شك.
Cities will coexist
المدن سوف تتعايش
in peaceful harmony.
في وئام سلمي.
In my lifetime,
في حياتي،
I will witness this day to come.
سوف أشهد هذا اليوم القادم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Here.
هنا.
What are you doing? Step back!
ماذا تفعل؟ تراجع!
It's alright. They're just starving.
لا بأس، إنهم فقط جائعون.
Here, one for you. And you.
هنا واحد لك. ولك.
Here.
هنا.
I know
أنا أعرف
you've been hungry for a long time
لقد كنت جائعا لفترة طويلة
and want food quickly,
وأريد الطعام بسرعة،
but rest assured.
ولكن كن مطمئنًا.
Once Jin City opens its gates,
بمجرد أن تفتح مدينة جين أبوابها،
we'll protect you
سوف نحميك
and won't abandon anyone.
ولن أتخلى عن أحد.
Please line up.
من فضلك إصطف.
Trust us.
ثق بنا.
Everyone will get food.
الجميع سيحصلون على الطعام.
One by one.
واحدا تلو الآخر.
My lady, our provisions
سيدتي، مؤنتنا
may be insufficient for the refugees.
قد لا يكون كافيا للاجئين.
I have some money.
لدي بعض المال.
Send someone to fetch more.
أرسل شخصًا لجلب المزيد.
Miss Yu, no need.
آنسة يو، لا حاجة لذلك.
My family has ample grain reserves.
تتمتع عائلتي باحتياطيات كبيرة من الحبوب.
I'll let someone send them over.
سأسمح لشخص ما بإرسالهم.
Mr. Song.
السيد سونغ.
It's okay, Miss Yu.
لا بأس، آنسة يو.
Helping you and City Lord through this crisis
مساعدتك أنت وسيد المدينة خلال هذه الأزمة
is my greatest joy.
هي أعظم فرحتي.
Okay.
تمام.
(City Lord's Mansion)
(قصر سيد المدينة)
Wei Feng, are the horses ready?
وي فينج، هل الخيول جاهزة؟
Yes.
نعم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Yuanbao, what's wrong?
يوانباو، ما الأمر؟
Why are they in a hurry?
لماذا هم في عجلة من أمرهم؟
They went to
لقد ذهبوا الى
deal with the granary issue.
التعامل مع قضية المخازن.
(Just as in my dream. The granary fell,)
(كما في حلمي، سقط المخزن)
(and they'll face a Mobei ambush on the way.)
(وسوف يواجهون كمينًا من موباي في الطريق.)
(I must catch up)
(يجب أن ألحق بالركب)
(to prevent the disaster.)
(لمنع الكارثة.)
Hyah!
هيا!
Wei Feng, how much longer?
وي فينج، إلى متى؟
Almost there, just after passing through this.
لقد وصلت تقريبا، فقط بعد المرور عبر هذا.
Hyah!
هيا!
Liu Bingmo, faster!
ليو بينغمو، أسرع!
Let's take the shortcut.
دعونا نأخذ الطريق المختصر.
Yes, my lady.
نعم سيدتي.
Hyah!
هيا!
(Yunqing, you must be safe.)
(يونتشينغ، يجب أن تكون آمنًا.)
Faster!
أسرع!
Liu Bingmo, what's wrong?
ليو بينغمو، ما الأمر؟
My lady, the carriage seems to be broken.
سيدتي، يبدو أن العربة مكسورة.
Why?
لماذا؟
I don't know. It suddenly stopped moving.
لا أعلم، لقد توقف فجأة عن الحركة.
Far from the main road?
بعيدة عن الطريق الرئيسي؟
Not far.
ليس بعيدا.
Just after the village ahead.
مباشرة بعد القرية أمامنا.
My lady.
سيدتي.
I'll go first.
سأذهب أولا.
Catch up to me later.
سألتقي بك لاحقًا.
Where's the village?
أين القرية؟
Anyone?
أي شخص؟
My lady.
سيدتي.
- Madam.
- سيدتي.
Wan.
فان.
Madam.
سيدتي.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Wan! Wan!
واو! واو!
Wan!
فان!
(You can't even protect the woman you love.)
(لا يمكنك حتى حماية المرأة التي تحبها.)
(Mu Yunqing, you're such a loser.)
(مو يونتشينغ، أنت خاسر حقًا.)
City Lord.
سيد المدينة.
Why was she there today?
لماذا كانت هناك اليوم؟
She learned you were heading to the granaries,
لقد علمت أنك كنت متجهًا إلى المخازن،
had to catch up to you,
كان علي أن ألحق بك،
and said you'd encounter danger.
وقال أنك ستواجه خطرًا.
Why she knows it?
لماذا تعرف ذلك؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I tried to escape last night to give you the token,
لقد حاولت الهروب الليلة الماضية لأعطيك الرمز،
but I was caught.
ولكن تم القبض علي.
(So she knew Eunuch Duan would come.)
(لذا فهي تعلم أن الخصي دوآن سوف يأتي.)
The token is gone.
الرمز ذهب.
Why didn't he give you trouble?
لماذا لم يسبب لك المتاعب؟
I thought I'd lost you again.
اعتقدت أنني فقدتك مرة أخرى.
(So she's also had)
(لذا فهي لديها أيضا)
(prophetic dreams like me.)
(أحلام نبوية مثلي.)
(Wan.)
(فان.)
(Why didn't you tell me?)
(لماذا لم تخبرني؟)
Wan.
فان.
Why were you there today?
لماذا كنت هناك اليوم؟
Did you foresee something?
هل توقعت شيئا؟
Yunqing, actually,
يون تشينغ، في الواقع،
I had a long dream before.
لقد حلمت بحلم طويل من قبل.
Most of it comes true in reality.
معظم ذلك يتحقق في الواقع.
Like today's danger you'd face on the road
مثل الخطر الذي قد تواجهه على الطريق اليوم
and Wei Feng's tragic death.
وموت وي فينج المأساوي.
I just wanted to prevent all this.
أردت فقط منع كل هذا.
Wan, how did we die in your dream?
وان كيف متنا في حلمك؟
In my dream...
في حلمي...
When I realized I could use
عندما أدركت أنني أستطيع استخدام
the dream contents as clues,
محتويات الحلم كدليل،
I wanted us to keep alive.
أردت أن نبقى على قيد الحياة.
Yunqing, I'm sorry.
يونتشينغ، أنا آسف.
But I never imagined all this
ولكنني لم أتخيل كل هذا أبدًا
would make us lose our child.
من شأنه أن يجعلنا نفقد طفلنا.
Yunqing, I'm sorry.
يونتشينغ، أنا آسف.
Wan, don't be sorry.
وان، لا تعتذر.
It's me...
هذا أنا...
Just let me be alone, okay?
فقط دعني أكون وحدي، حسنًا؟
I need some time.
أحتاج إلى بعض الوقت.
Give me some time
أعطني بعض الوقت
to let me stay by myself, alright?
لكي أبقى بمفردي، حسنًا؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll be fine.
سوف أكون بخير.
♪The moon rests on the treetops, listening to the evening breeze♪
♪يستقر القمر على قمم الأشجار، ويستمع إلى نسيم المساء♪
♪Wine in hand, I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪ النبيذ في يدي، أغني بينما تتألق النجوم في حالة من الفوضى ♪
♪The endless night keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪الليل الذي لا ينتهي لا يحتفظ إلا بمصباح وحيد♪
(So I'm not the only one experiencing Four Dreams.)
(لذا فأنا لست الوحيد الذي يعاني من الأحلام الأربعة.)
(Even my beloved is trapped in this loop.)
(حتى حبيبتي وقعت في هذه الحلقة.)
(Why has fate ordained this?)
(لماذا قدر القدر هذا؟)
(Why involve Wan in all this?)
(لماذا إشراك وان في كل هذا؟)
(Why make us meet repeatedly in dreams)
(لماذا تجعلنا نلتقي مراراً وتكراراً في الأحلام)
(only to watch each other get hurt?)
(فقط لمشاهدة بعضهم البعض يتأذون؟)
♪Beyond words♪
♪ما وراء الكلمات♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪إن العهد يُعتز به في كل الأوقات♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪بعض النفوس تتوق إلى تخمير الوقت♪
♪Into a story♪
♪في قصة♪
♪Crushing the past, I let old memories fade♪
♪سحق الماضي، أترك الذكريات القديمة تتلاشى♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
♪لا تدع هذه القصة تنتهي♪
♪Winter snow waltzes before the courtyard♪
♪رقصة ثلوج الشتاء أمام الفناء♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪القصور لا ترحم♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪يتطلب الأمر الكثير من الشجاعة♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪لإعادة تتبع كل خطوة♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪همسات الذاكرة، أحلام أو وهم♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪الفراشات تتسلق الجبال من أجل الحب♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪يموت قبل الزهور♪
♪You seem so distant, yet right before my eyes♪
♪تبدو بعيدًا جدًا، ومع ذلك، أمام عيني مباشرة♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪لعبة شطرنج، مصير الصراع♪
♪I dream of standing with you, side by side♪
♪أحلم بالوقوف معك جنبًا إلى جنب♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪إذا قابلتني وجها لوجه♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪سأموت دون ندم واحد♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪أنت النجم الذي لا يمكن المساس به♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪من خلال كل موجات الحب والكراهية♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪التقت أعيننا عبر العالم البشري♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪عندما تحركت النسمات بجانب نافذتي♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪أزهار الكرز أمطرت السماء♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪أنت النجم البعيد♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪أنا أصغر بقعة♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪أقضي كل إخلاصي♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪لدموعك وعناقك♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪سأتحدى كل العواصف الثلجية♪
♪To walk with you♪
♪للمشي معك♪